(Sheldon:)I know,
that's why I shortened it.
What do you want?
(Sheldon:)I came to go over your alibi
for last night.
(Leonard:)What alibi?
(Sheldon:)You've asked me
(Sheldon:)to lie on your behalf,
and as you know,
(Sheldon:)I am deeply uncomfortable
with impromptu dishonesty,
(Sheldon:)so I've provided you
with an ironclad alibi.
(Sheldon:)You couldn't have spent
last night with Priya
(Sheldon:)because you were
with another woman.
(Leonard:)Oh, I'm so sure
I'm gonna regret this,
(Leonard:)but who was I with?
The fun-loving and morally loose
Miss Maggie McGarry.
(Leonard:)Oh, God.
(Sheldon:)You met her at Pasadena's most
popular Irish watering hole,
(Sheldon:)Lucky Baldwin's, where Maggie
spends her nights tending bar
(Sheldon:)with a head full of curls
and a heart full of dreams.
"Leonard, call me if you
are interested in coitus.
(Leonard(reading a napkin Sheldon has handed him):)Sincerely,
Maggie McGarry."
(Sheldon:)And if anyone were
(Sheldon:)to actually call that number,
they will hear this.